// hiragana.js
export const hiraganaData = [
  { "id": 1, "question": "あ", "correctAnswer": "a" },
  { "id": 2, "question": "い", "correctAnswer": "i" },
  { "id": 3, "question": "う", "correctAnswer": "u" },
  { "id": 4, "question": "え", "correctAnswer": "e" },
  { "id": 5, "question": "お", "correctAnswer": "o" },
  { "id": 6, "question": "か", "correctAnswer": "ka" },
  { "id": 7, "question": "き", "correctAnswer": "ki" },
  { "id": 8, "question": "く", "correctAnswer": "ku" },
  { "id": 9, "question": "け", "correctAnswer": "ke" },
  { "id": 10, "question": "こ", "correctAnswer": "ko" },
  { "id": 11, "question": "さ", "correctAnswer": "sa" },
  { "id": 12, "question": "し", "correctAnswer": "shi" },
  { "id": 13, "question": "す", "correctAnswer": "su" },
  { "id": 14, "question": "せ", "correctAnswer": "se" },
  { "id": 15, "question": "そ", "correctAnswer": "so" },
  { "id": 16, "question": "た", "correctAnswer": "ta" },
  { "id": 17, "question": "ち", "correctAnswer": "chi" },
  { "id": 18, "question": "つ", "correctAnswer": "tsu" },
  { "id": 19, "question": "て", "correctAnswer": "te" },
  { "id": 20, "question": "と", "correctAnswer": "to" },
  { "id": 21, "question": "な", "correctAnswer": "na" },
  { "id": 22, "question": "に", "correctAnswer": "ni" },
  { "id": 23, "question": "ぬ", "correctAnswer": "nu" },
  { "id": 24, "question": "ね", "correctAnswer": "ne" },
  { "id": 25, "question": "の", "correctAnswer": "no" },
  { "id": 26, "question": "は", "correctAnswer": "ha" },
  { "id": 27, "question": "ひ", "correctAnswer": "hi" },
  { "id": 28, "question": "ふ", "correctAnswer": "fu" },
  { "id": 29, "question": "へ", "correctAnswer": "he" },
  { "id": 30, "question": "ほ", "correctAnswer": "ho" },
  { "id": 31, "question": "ま", "correctAnswer": "ma" },
  { "id": 32, "question": "み", "correctAnswer": "mi" },
  { "id": 33, "question": "む", "correctAnswer": "mu" },
  { "id": 34, "question": "め", "correctAnswer": "me" },
  { "id": 35, "question": "も", "correctAnswer": "mo" },
  { "id": 36, "question": "や", "correctAnswer": "ya" },
  { "id": 37, "question": "ゆ", "correctAnswer": "yu" },
  { "id": 38, "question": "よ", "correctAnswer": "yo" },
  { "id": 39, "question": "ら", "correctAnswer": "ra" },
  { "id": 40, "question": "り", "correctAnswer": "ri" },
  { "id": 41, "question": "る", "correctAnswer": "ru" },
  { "id": 42, "question": "れ", "correctAnswer": "re" },
  { "id": 43, "question": "ろ", "correctAnswer": "ro" },
  { "id": 44, "question": "わ", "correctAnswer": "wa" },
  { "id": 45, "question": "を", "correctAnswer": "wo" },
  { "id": 46, "question": "ん", "correctAnswer": "n" }
  ];
  